Guide to the Yale University Library Name/Title Card Catalog
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Space and f. (Box 7410)
- Spafford (Box 7411)
- Spain. Comision (Box 7412)
- Spain. Instituto nacional (Box 7413)
- Spain. Seccion (Box 7414)
- Spalding (titles, etc.) (Box 7415)
- Spanish comedy (Box 7416)
- Spark, W. (Box 7417)
- Spasov, D. (Box 7418)
- Speaking of the w. (Box 7419)
- Special-K (Box 7420)
- Special study (Box 7421)
- Spectator (Box 7422)
- Speech (Box 7423)
- Speer, W. (Box 7424)
- Spence (Box 7425)
- Spencer, Herbert, 1820-1903 (author) (Box 7426)
- Spencer, W. (Box 7427)
- Spenser, Edmund, 1552?-1599. Faerie Queen (continued) (Box 7428)
- Spermata (Box 7429)
- Spheres of j. (Box 7430)
- Spiegelberg (Box 7431)
- Spiess, G. (Box 7432)
- Spinelli, B. (Box 7433)
- Spinoza, Benedictus de, 1632-1677 (subject) (T) (Box 7434)
- Spirit song. (Box 7435)
- Spitteler n. (Box 7436)
- Spoehr (Box 7437)
- Spoljna (Box 7438)
- Sport of the h. (Box 7439)
- Sprache im p. (Box 7440)
- Sprague, J. (Box 7441)
- Sprecher (Box 7442)
- Spring rains (Box 7443)
- Springfield (titles, etc.) (Box 7444)
- Spuler, C. (Box 7445)
- Squatting (Box 7446)
- Srdce (Box 7447)
- Srbija (Box 7448)
- Srpska akademija nauka i umetnosti (Box 7449)
- Srpski etnografski zbornik; knj. 68. (Box 7450)
- Ssu fang (Box 7451)
- Ssu k'u ch'uean shu chen (Box 7452)
- Ssu-ma, Ch'ien, ca. 145-ca. 86 B.C. Shih-chi (continued) (Box 7453)
- Ssu shih i chi (Box 7454)
- Staaten (Box 7455)
- Staatliche Museen zu Berlin. E... (Box 7456)
- Staatsgalerie Stuttgart. G. (Box 7457)
- Stacey (Box 7458)
- Stadler, H. (Box 7459)
- Staeckel (Box 7460)
- Staehlin (Box 7461)
- Stafford, W. (Box 7462)
- Stahl, G. (Box 7463)
- Staley (Box 7464)
- Stall (Box 7465)
- Stammler (Box 7466)
- Stancombe, G. (Box 7467)
- Standard Oil Company of New York (Box 7468)
- Stanford (surname) (Box 7469)
- Stanford University. English club (Box 7470)
- Stanhope, Philip Henry. S. (Box 7471)
- Stanley (surname) (Box 7472)
- Stanley, V. (Box 7473)
- Stanton, T. (Box 7474)
- Star reporters (Box 7475)
- Stark, H. (Box 7476)
- Staros, J. (Box 7477)
- Start (Box 7478)
- State and status (Box 7479)
- State Historical Society of Wisconsin. Library (Box 7480)
- State rights (titles, etc.) (Box 7481)
- Statements (Box 7482)
- Stat'i i rechi (Box 7483)
- Statistical office (Box 7484)
- Statistics for t. (Box 7485)
- Statistique du d. (Box 7486)
- Statna (Box 7487)
- Statystyka (Box 7488)
- Stavenhagen (Box 7489)
- Steamer (Box 7490)
- Stech (Box 7491)
- Steel (surname) (Box 7492)
- Steele, Richard (subject) (Box 7493)
- Steer, H. (Box 7494)
- Stefanovic, S. (Box 7495)
- Stegner, P. (Box 7496)
- Stein, C. (Box 7497)
- Stein, I. (Box 7498)
- Steinbeck, John, 1902- (author) (L) (Box 7499)
- Steine (Box 7500)
- Steiner, Rudolf, 1861-1925 (subject) (Box 7501)
- Steinman, E. (Box 7502)
- Stekhoven (Box 7503)
- Stemmer, W. (Box 7504)
- Stendhal (subject) (S) (Box 7505)
- Stent (Box 7506)
- Stephan, O. (Box 7507)
- Stephens (Box 7508)
- Stephens, W. (Box 7509)
- Sterba, E. (Box 7510)
- Stern, E. (Box 7511)
- Stern, V. (Box 7512)
- Sterne, Laurence (subject) (Box 7513)
- Stetler, H. (Box 7514)
- Stevens (Box 7515)
- Stevens, John (Box 7516)
- Stevens, William Chase (Box 7517)
- Stevenson, P. (Box 7518)
- Stevenson, Robert Louis (Individual works) Prayer (Box 7519)
- Stevick, R. (Box 7520)
- Stewart, E. (Box 7521)
- Stewart, Mary (Box 7522)
- Stiasny (Box 7523)
- Stieda (Box 7524)
- Stift K. (Box 7525)
- Stigma (Box 7526)
- Still house (Box 7527)
- Stilwell (Box 7528)
- Stipp (Box 7529)
- Sto (Box 7530)
- Stockdale (Box 7531)
- Stockholm International Peace Research Institute. O. (Box 7532)
- Stockton, Frank Richard. Rudder Grange (Box 7533)
- Stoddart (Box 7534)
- Stoever (Box 7535)
- Stokell, G. (Box 7536)
- Stoland (Box 7537)
- Stolt, H. (Box 7538)
- Stone, G. (Box 7539)
- Stone, W. (Box 7540)
- Stooker, W. (Box 7541)
- Storey (Box 7542)
- Storia do (Box 7543)
- Storm, Gustav (Box 7544)
- Storrs, Ronald (Box 7545)
- Story of I. (Box 7546)
- Stothart (Box 7547)
- Stow (Box 7548)
- Strabo (Box 7549)
- Straelen (Box 7550)
- Stralenberg (Box 7551)
- Strange story (Box 7552)
- Strashun, S. (Box 7553)
- Strategies for p. (Box 7554)
- Stratigraphic e. (Box 7555)
- Strauss (Box 7556)
- Strauss, W. (Box 7557)
- Streatfield, H. (Box 7558)
- Streeter (Box 7559)
- Strelich, T. (Box 7560)
- Stricker (Box 7561)
- Strindberg, August (author) (Box 7562)
- Strobel, A. (Box 7563)
- Strohm (Box 7564)
- Strong, Josiah (Box 7565)
- Stroschein, F. (Box 7566)
- Structural design (Box 7567)
- Structure of m. (Box 7568)
- Strugggle for P. (Box 7569)
- Strumilin (Box 7570)
- Struyck (Box 7571)
- Stuart, H. (Box 7572)
- Stubbe, L. (Box 7573)
- Studdert (Box 7574)
- Student's history (Box 7575)
- Studi e saggi (Box 7576)
- Studi T. (Box 7577)
- Studia humaniora (Box 7578)
- Studia pomorskie (Box 7579)
- Studien (Box 7580)
- Studien zur (Box 7581)
- Studien zur Geschichte des (Box 7582)
- Studien zur S. (Box 7583)
- Studies in African literature (Box 7584)
- Studies in citizen (Box 7585)
- Studies in English literature (London, E. Arnold) (Box 7586)
- Studies in industrial (Box 7587)
- Studies in mass (Box 7588)
- Studies in philosophy and s. (Box 7589)
- Studies in social work (Box 7590)
- Studies in the n. (Box 7591)
- Studies of s. (Box 7592)
- Studies on w. (Box 7593)
- Study (Box 7594)
- Study of power (Box 7595)
- Stuelcken (Box 7596)
- Stunde N. (Box 7597)
- Sturm, K. (Box 7598)
- Stuttgart. K. (Box 7599)
- Stylistics (Box 7600)
- Su lien (Box 7601)
- Su un (Box 7602)
- Suarez Lopez, G. (Box 7603)
- Subhasila (Box 7604)
- Subrahmanyam, K. (Box 7605)
- Successful w. (Box 7606)
- Sucre, V. (Box 7607)
- Sudermann, Hermann (author) (Box 7608)
- Sue, Eugene (subject) (Box 7609)
- Sueno en (Box 7610)
- Suffolk County, N.Y. (Box 7611)
- Suger (Box 7612)
- Sugyot m. (Box 7613)
- Suidafrikaanse j. (Box 7614)
- Sukenick, R. (Box 7615)
- Sularto, B. (Box 7616)
- Sullivan, A. (Box 7617)
- Sullivan, R. (Box 7618)
- Sultze, C. (Box 7619)
- Sumec (Box 7620)
- Summer (Box 7621)
- Summers, H. (Box 7622)
- Sumner, Willliam Graham. Lecture (Box 7623)
- Sun, I. (Box 7624)
- Sun, Yat-sen (author) (Box 7625)
- Sun, Yeh-fang (Box 7626)
- Sun Yatsin, A. (Box 7627)
- Sundermeyer, N. (Box 7628)
- Sung, Hsi-pin (Box 7629)
- Sung, T. (Box 7630)
- Sunrise (Box 7631)
- Suomen (Box 7632)
- Super, M. (Box 7633)
- Supko, P. (Box 7634)
- Supply w. (Box 7635)
- Suraci, A. (Box 7636)
- Surguchev (Box 7637)
- Surrey (surname) (Box 7638)
- Survey of Federal Archives (Box 7639)
- Surveys of G. (Box 7640)
- Suslo, L. (Box 7641)
- Sutcliffe, P. (Box 7642)
- Sutirto, S. (Box 7643)
- Sutton, P. (Box 7644)
- Suwayd, Y. (Box 7645)
- Suzuki, Kohe (Box 7646)
- Svane, G. (Box 7647)
- Svenska autograf (Box 7648)
- Svenska saellskapet (Box 7649)
- Sveriges o. (Box 7650)
- Sviatnoi, F. (Box 7651)
- Swaen (Box 7652)
- Swan, R. (Box 7653)
- Swart (Box 7654)
- Sweden (author) (Box 7655)
- Sweden. Nationalmuseum (Box 7656)
- Sweden. Statistiska Centralbyran. So. (Box 7657)
- Swedenborg, Emanuel (subject) (Box 7658)
- Sweet, J. (Box 7659)
- Swem (Box 7660)
- Swift (Box 7661)
- Swift, Jonathan (individual works) Satire (Box 7662)
- Swinburne, Algernon Charles (author) (Box 7663)
- Swinnerton, H. (Box 7664)
- Switzerland. Laws, statutes, etc. (Box 7665)
- Syamali (Box 7666)
- Sydserff, T. (Box 7667)
- Sylva (Box 7668)
- Symbolic w. (Box 7669)
- Symonds, John Addington, 1840-1893. Shelley (Box 7670)
- Symposium (Box 7671)
- Symposium on Birds (Box 7672)
- Symposium on Food (Box 7673)
- Symposium on Molluscs (Box 7674)
- Symposium on River (Box 7675)
- Symposium on the Mineral (Box 7676)
- Sympson (Box 7677)
- Synkowski, D. (Box 7678)
- Syo-ki (Box 7679)
- Syrische (Box 7680)
- Systematics of M. (Box 7681)
- Szabo, J. (Box 7682)
- Szczerba, W. (Box 7683)
- Szeponik, H. (Box 7684)
- Szombathy (Box 7685)
- Szymoszek, E. (Box 7686)
- T.R. (Box 7687)
- Ta fang k. (Box 7688)
- Ta lu tsao (Box 7689)
- Taamuli (Box 7690)
- Tabi to kyodo (Box 7691)
- Tabora, P. (Box 7692)
- Tacitus, Cornelius (author) (Box 7693)
- Tacitus, Cornelius. Historiae (Box 7694)
- Tadevosian, V. (Box 7695)
- Tafsir (Box 7696)
- Tagebuch e. (Box 7697)
- Tagore, S. (Box 7698)
- Tai, Ch'i (Box 7699)
- T'ai pai (Box 7700)
- T'ai-wan (Box 7701)
- T'ai-wan min pao (Box 7702)
- T'ai-wan ta hsueh, T'ai-pei. College of Arts (Box 7703)
- T'ai-wan yue lei (Box 7704)
- Taillandier (Box 7705)
- Taire, L. (Box 7706)
- Taiwan. Hsin (Box 7707)
- Taj (Box 7708)
- Takahashi (Box 7709)
- Takakura, T. (Box 7710)
- Takata (Box 7711)
- Takeda, Y. (Box 7712)
- Takeuchi, Toshimi (Box 7713)
- Taksi (Box 7714)
- Talbot, M. (Box 7715)
- Tales of a cruel... (Box 7716)
- Talkative (Box 7717)
- Tallman (Box 7718)
- Talmud (texts) (E) (Box 7719)
- Talmud (texts) Sukah (Box 7720)
- Talmud (subject) (Criticism, etc.) (L) (Box 7721)
- Tam, L. (Box 7722)
- Tamayo, Jose (Box 7723)
- Tamm (Box 7724)
- T'an, Cheng-pi. (Box 7725)
- T'an shih (Box 7726)
- Tanaka (Box 7727)
- Tanaka Tadao (Box 7728)
- Tang ch'ien sheng cheng ti (Box 7729)
- T'ang Ming l. (Box 7730)
- Tang tai hsiao (Box 7731)
- T'ang, Yung-t'ung (Box 7732)
- Taniguchi, M. (Box 7733)
- Tannenbaum, F. (Box 7734)
- Tansillo (Box 7735)
- Tanzania: p. (Box 7736)
- T'ao hua (Box 7737)
- Tap s. (Box 7738)
- Tapson (Box 7739)
- Tarbell (Box 7740)
- Targum. Pentateuch (Box 7741)
- Tarind (Box 7742)
- Taro (Box 7743)
- Tartu R. (Box 7744)
- Tasdik (Box 7745)
- Tassinari (Box 7746)
- Tata Institute of S. (Box 7747)
- Tate Gallery (Box 7748)
- Tatler (Box 7749)
- Tauber (Box 7750)
- Tausch (Box 7751)
- Taverny (Box 7752)
- Tax Foundation (Box 7753)
- Tayama Kwa-tai (Box 7754)
- Taylor, Belle (Box 7755)
- Taylor, Foster (Box 7756)
- Taylor, Isaac (Box 7757)
- Taylor, John, 1580-1653. H. (Box 7758)
- Taylor, Mildred (Box 7759)
- Taylor, T. (Box 7760)
- Taylor, Zachary, 1784-1850 (Box 7761)
- Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich, 1840-1893. Symphonie (Box 7762)
- Teach (Box 7763)
- Teaching of the T. (Box 7764)
- Teatr z. (Box 7765)
- Teatro: Un r. (Box 7766)
- Technician (Box 7767)
- Technological developments (Box 7768)
- Tecwyn (Box 7769)
- Tegner (Box 7770)
- Teikoku kempo t. (Box 7771)
- Teitge, J. (Box 7772)
- Teksty (Box 7773)
- Teleshov (Box 7774)
- Telles, B. (Box 7775)
- Temasha (Box 7776)
- Tempi m. (Box 7777)
- Temple of Jerusalem (Box 7778)
- Temps des a. (Box 7779)
- Tena, L. (Box 7780)
- Teng (Box 7781)
- Teng, Yen-fang (Box 7782)
- Tennessee. Department of p. (Box 7783)
- Tenniel, Sir John (Box 7784)
- Tennyson, Alfred, 1809-1892 (subject) (R) (Box 7785)
- Tenrikyo (Box 7786)
- Teoremas (Box 7787)
- Tepper (Box 7788)
- Terence (Works) (Box 7789)
- Teresa, L. (Box 7790)
- Terminologie m. (Box 7791)
- Terranglia (Box 7792)
- Territoires (Box 7793)
- Terry l. (Box 7794)
- Terwiel (Box 7795)
- Tessiner (Box 7796)
- Testimonianze del... (Box 7797)
- Tetsugen (Box 7798)
- Tew (Box 7799)
- Texas. Department of e. (Box 7800)
- Texas (titles, etc.) (Box 7801)
- Texas monthly (Box 7802)
- Textbook of o. (Box 7803)
- Textes et e. (Box 7804)
- Texts c. (Box 7805)
- Thackeray, Wm. M., 1811-1863 (Individual works) (Box 7806)
- Thai-Bach (Box 7807)
- Thailand. Krom R. (Box 7808)
- Thailand. Samnakngan Sathiti... (Box 7809)
- Tham (Box 7810)
- Thanom (Box 7811)
- That's the s. (Box 7812)
- The (Box 7813)
- Theaterdichter (Box 7814)
- Theatrum t. (Box 7815)
- Thelen (Box 7816)
- Theobald, W. (Box 7817)
- Theodoret, Bishop of Cyrrhus (Box 7818)
- Theologie historique, 63. (Box 7819)
- Theophylacti (Box 7820)
- Theorie und Praxis des T. (Box 7821)
- Theory of e. (Box 7822)
- Therapeutic p. (Box 7823)
- Thermolampe (Box 7824)
- Thesoro (Box 7825)
- They were (Box 7826)
- Thiel, T. (Box 7827)
- Thierry, N. (Box 7828)
- Thin p. (Box 7829)
- Third world (Box 7830)
- This and (Box 7831)
- Thissen (Box 7832)
- Thomae (Box 7833)
- Thomas Aquinas, Saint (subject) (D) (Box 7834)
- Thomas, Earl of D. (Box 7835)
- Thomas, Clarence (Box 7836)
- Thomas, Franz (Box 7837)
- Thomas, John (Box 7838)
- Thomas, O. (Box 7839)
- Thomas, William S. (Box 7840)
- Thomas-Stanford (Box 7841)
- Thompson, Benjamin (Box 7842)
- Thompson, Edward J. (Box 7843)
- Thompson, I. (Box 7844)
- Thompson, Lawrence S. (Box 7845)
- Thompson, Slason (Box 7846)
- Thomsen, F. (Box 7847)
- Thomson, James, 1700-1748 (author) (Box 7848)
- Thomson, R. (Box 7849)
- Thorburn, E. (Box 7850)
- Thorlac (Box 7851)
- Thornford (Box 7852)
- Thorp (Box 7853)
- Those Great Cowboy Sidekicks (Box 7854)
- Thouverez (Box 7855)
- Three h. (Box 7856)
- Three to o. (Box 7857)
- Through p. (Box 7858)
- Thucydides (translations) (S) (Box 7859)
- Thunder f. (Box 7860)
- Thuroczy (Box 7861)
- Thyone (Box 7862)
- Ti i t. (Box 7863)
- Tibal (Box 7864)
- Tice (Box 7865)
- Tidy (Box 7866)
- Tielt (Box 7867)
- T'ien-fei (Box 7868)
- Tien t. (Box 7869)
- Tiepolo, J. (Box 7870)
- Tieu (Box 7871)
- Tijdschrift voor f. (Box 7872)
- Tilawat (Box 7873)
- Tillich, Paul, 1886-1965 (R) (Box 7874)
- Tilman (Box 7875)
- Time (Box 7876)
- Time of m. (Box 7877)
- Times of c. (Box 7878)
- Timoner (Box 7879)
- Tincal (Box 7880)
- Ting, Ling, 1907- (Box 7881)
- Tinker (Box 7882)
- Tipitaka, Suttapitaka. M. (Box 7883)
- Tiroler Landesmuseum (Box 7884)
- Tisset (Box 7885)
- Title (Box 7886)
- Titus (Box 7887)
- Tjerita (Box 7888)
- To C. (Box 7889)
- To t. (Box 7890)
- To youth (Box 7891)
- Tobias, Valentin (Box 7892)
- Tocqueville (Box 7893)
- Todd, D. (Box 7894)
- Todo B. (Box 7895)
- Toepffer (Box 7896)
- Togliatti a S. (Box 7897)
- Toita (Box 7898)
- Tokiwai (Box 7899)
- Tokutomi (Box 7900)
- Tokyo. Tokei (Box 7901)
- Tokyo Daigaku. University (Box 7902)
- Tokyo-shi (Box 7903)
- Toledo (surname) (Box 7904)
- Tollard (Box 7905)
- Tolstoi i (Box 7906)
- Tolstoi, Lev Nikolaevich (subject) (H) (Box 7907)
- Toma (Box 7908)
- Tombeur (Box 7909)
- Tomkins, S. (Box 7910)
- Tomoeda (Box 7911)
- Tonan Ajia m. (Box 7912)
- Toninelli (Box 7913)
- Tooker (Box 7914)
- Topham (Box 7915)
- Topological p. (Box 7916)
- Torberg (Box 7917)
- Torlesse (Box 7918)
- Toronto Public Library (Box 7919)
- Torrealba (Box 7920)
- Torres C. (Box 7921)
- Torrie (Box 7922)
- Tosaka (Box 7923)
- Tosi, P. (Box 7924)
- Totton (Box 7925)
- Toulouse (surname) (Box 7926)
- Touring (Box 7927)
- Toursier (Box 7928)
- Tovell (Box 7929)
- Towards a new (Box 7930)
- Tower bridge (Box 7931)
- Towne, F. (Box 7932)
- Townsend, S. (Box 7933)
- Toynbee (Box 7934)
- Toyo shi (titles) (Box 7935)
- Tozzi, P. (Box 7936)
- Tracks in art (Box 7937)
- Trade and intercourse (Box 7938)
- Tradicia (Box 7939)
- Traditions of R. (Box 7940)
- Tragedy (titles, etc.) Tragedy of the O. (Box 7941)
- Train, C. (Box 7942)
- Traite t. (Box 7943)
- Tran, V. (Box 7944)
- Trans-continental (Box 7945)
- Transition y. (Box 7946)
- Transparence (Box 7947)
- Transvaal m. (Box 7948)
- Trask (Box 7949)
- Traupel (Box 7950)
- Travaux de r. (Box 7951)
- Traveler's library (Box 7952)
- Travis (Box 7953)
- Treasures of J. (Box 7954)
- Treatment of h. (Box 7955)
- Treece, R. (Box 7956)
- Trelawny (Box 7957)
- Trenchard, J. (Box 7958)
- Trent (Box 7959)
- Tres siglos (Box 7960)
- Treuge (Box 7961)
- Trevor-Roper (Box 7962)
- Trial of the a. (Box 7963)
- Tribune (Box 7964)
- Trier (Box 7965)
- Trigunayat (Box 7966)
- Trinchant (Box 7967)
- Trinity Lutheran (Box 7968)
- Tripitaka. Sutrapitaka (R) (Box 7969)
- Tristan-Drama (Box 7970)
- Trivandrum Sanskrit series (Box 7971)
- Troemner (Box 7972)
- Troj (Box 7973)
- Trommer (Box 7974)
- Tropoiu (Box 7975)
- Trotter, T. (Box 7976)
- Trowbridge (Box 7977)
- Trubiani (Box 7978)
- Trudy A. (Box 7979)
- True f. (Box 7980)
- Trueman (Box 7981)
- Truman, M. (Box 7982)
- Trumps (Box 7983)
- Truth i. (Box 7984)
- Ts (Box 7985)
- Tsai feng h. (Box 7986)
- Ts'ai, T. (Box 7987)
- Ts'ang (Box 7988)
- Tsao-han (Box 7989)
- Tsao ti s. (Box 7990)
- Tschermak (Box 7991)
- Ts'en, W. (Box 7992)
- Tseng, Kuang-i (Box 7993)
- TSentral'nyi gosudarstvennyi arkhiv narodnogo khoziaistva SSSR (continued) (Box 7994)
- Tsing (Box 7995)
- Tso p'in c. (Box 7996)
- Tsou, Y. (Box 7997)
- Tsuchiya, T. (Box 7998)
- Ts'ui, Shu-ch'in (Box 7999)
- Tsukui, T. (Box 8000)
- Ts'ung shu chi ch'eng hsu pien, 8 (Box 8001)
- Tsushima s. (Box 8002)
- Tu, Chu (Box 8003)
- Tu-Kuang, S. (Box 8004)
- Tu ta-sao (Box 8005)
- Tuan, Shu-an. (Box 8006)
- Tucker, B. (Box 8007)
- Tuckerman (Box 8008)
- Tudor s. (Box 8009)
- Tuercke (Box 8010)
- Tugas (Box 8011)
- Tulaci (Box 8012)
- Tulsi (Box 8013)
- Tuncel (Box 8014)
- Tung-fang, W. (Box 8015)
- T'ung, Nancy (Box 8016)
- T'ung, Wen (Box 8017)
- Tunnawi (Box 8018)
- Turati (Box 8019)
- Turgenev, Ivan Sergieevich (Author) (Individual Works) (F) (Box 8020)
- Turin. R. (Box 8021)
- Turkmenistan (Box 8022)
- Turner (surname) (Box 8023)
- Turner, H. (Box 8024)
- Turner, John S. (Box 8025)
- Turner, William Aldren (Box 8026)
- Turri (Box 8027)
- Tuson (Box 8028)
- Tuttle, T. (Box 8029)
- Tvorchestvo M. (Box 8030)
- Twain, Mark, 1835-1910 (Correspondence) (P) (Box 8031)
- Twayne's E. (Box 8032)
- Twelve d. (Box 8033)
- Twentieth century T. (Box 8034)
- Twin G. (Box 8035)
- Two g. (Box 8036)
- Two summer (Box 8037)
- Tydeman (Box 8038)
- Tyler, W. (Box 8039)
- Typefounders' (Box 8040)
- Tyrolese (Box 8041)
- Tzara (Box 8042)
- Tzu-jen (Box 8043)
- UCI (Box 8044)
- UNICEF (Box 8045)
- US coal (Box 8046)
- USS Henry (Box 8047)
- Ubh (Box 8048)
- Uchida, S. (Box 8049)
- Udelson, Jerri (Box 8050)
- Ueber die Ursachen (Box 8051)
- Ueda, Kazutoshi (Box 8052)
- Ufa (Box 8053)
- Uggla (Box 8054)
- Uhler (Box 8055)
- Ujfalvy (Box 8056)
- Ukrainian C. (Box 8057)
- Ukrains'ki narodni v. (Box 8058)
- Ulfah (Box 8059)
- Ulloa (Box 8060)
- Ulrich, K. (Box 8061)
- Ultrasonics international (Box 8062)
- Umas (Box 8063)
- Umetnost (Box 8064)
- Unamuno, Miguel de (continued) (Box 8065)
- Uncle Piper (Box 8066)
- Under the waves (Box 8067)
- Understanding f. (Box 8068)
- Undset (Box 8069)
- UNESCO (publications) (I) (Box 8070)
- UNESCO. General Conference (Box 8071)
- Unforgettable e. (Box 8072)
- Unger, R. (Box 8073)
- Unification church (Box 8074)
- Union club (Box 8075)
- Union list of serials (Box 8076)
- Union postale (Box 8077)
- Unita i. (Box 8078)
- United brotherhood (Box 8079)
- United Lutheran Church (Box 8080)
- United Nations. Department of Public Information (Box 8081)
- United Nations. Economic Commission for Latin America (continued) (Box 8082)
- United Nations (subject) (Box 8083)
- United Nations-Asia (Box 8084)
- United Nations Conference on Trade and Development. Secretariat (Box 8085)
- United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration. European Regional Office (Box 8086)
- United service (Box 8087)
- United States (author) Constitution. Amendments. 18th (Box 8088)
- United States (laws, statutes, etc.) Immigration laws (Box 8089)
- United States (laws, statutes, etc.) 1793-1795 (3d Congress) (Box 8090)
- United States, plaintiff (Box 8091)
- United States. Agricultural Research Service (Box 8092)
- United States. Army. A.E.F. Air service (Box 8093)
- United States. Army. Department (Box 8094)
- United States. Army (subject) (Box 8095)
- United States. Army-Registers (Box 8096)
- United States. Atomic Energy Commission. Nuclear (Box 8097)
- United States. Bureau of fisheries (Box 8098)
- United States. Bureau of mines (Box 8099)
- United States. Bureau of the census (Box 8100)
- United States. Central Intelligence Agency (Box 8101)
- United States. Civil service commission (Box 8102)
- United States. Committee (Box 8103)
- United States. Congress. Joint Economic Committee. P (Box 8104)
- United States. Congress-Powers and duties (Box 8105)
- United States. Congress. House. Committee on Indian Affairs (Box 8106)
- United States. Congress. House. Select Committee on Small Business (Box 8107)
- United States. Congress. Senate. Committee on Immigration (Box 8108)
- United States. Congress. Senate-Addresses, essays, lectures (Box 8109)
- United States. Continental Congress (subject) (Box 8110)
- United States. Department of Agriculture (subject) (Box 8111)
- United States. Department of Housing and Urban Development. Report (Box 8112)
- United States. Department of State. Despatches from United States consuls in Georgetown... (Box 8113)
- United States. Department of State. Message of... (Box 8114)
- United States. Department of State (subject) (U) (Box 8115)
- United States. Department of the Interior. Division (Box 8116)
- United States. District Court. New York (Box 8117)
- United States. Environmental Protection Agency. Environmental m. (Box 8118)
- United States. Federal Emergency Relief Administration (Box 8119)
- United States. Food administration (Box 8120)
- United States. General land office (Box 8121)
- United States. Inspector-general's office (Box 8122)
- United States. Labor, Bureau of (Box 8123)
- United States. National Aeronautics and Space Administration. High... (Box 8124)
- United States. National Commission (Box 8125)
- United States. National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration. Air Resources... (Box 8126)
- United States. Naval Academy (subject) (Box 8127)
- United States. Navy-Illustrations (Box 8128)
- United States. Office of Defense Transportation (Box 8129)
- United States. Office of Naval Research. List (Box 8130)
- United States. Ordinance Department (Box 8131)
- United States. President (1881: Garfield) (Box 8132)
- United States. Public Health Service. Division of E. (Box 8133)
- United States. Shipping Board (Box 8134)
- United States. Supreme Court (author) Federal rules (Box 8135)
- United States. Tariff Commission (author) (Box 8136)
- United States. War Department (author) Report (Box 8137)
- United States. Works Projects Administration. Minnesota (Box 8138)
- United States Christian Commission (Box 8139)
- United States Housing Authority (Box 8140)
- United States Naval Observatory (Box 8141)
- United States-Taiwan (Box 8142)
- Universal magazine (Box 8143)
- Universidad Catolica de Chile (Box 8144)
- Universidad de Chile (Box 8145)
- Universidad de La Habana. F (continued) (Box 8146)
- Universidad de San Carlos de Guatemala (Box 8147)
- Universidad e. (Box 8148)
- Universidad Nacional Autonoma de Mexico. Instituto de Investigaciones Filosoficas (Box 8149)
- Universidad Nacional de Colombia (Box 8150)
- Universidad Nacional de Tucuman (Box 8151)
- Universidade de Coimbra. I. (Box 8152)
- Universita (Box 8153)
- Universita degli studi di Trieste. Instituto di E. (Box 8154)
- Universita di Firenze (Box 8155)
- Universita di Padova (Box 8156)
- Universita di Roma. Instituto di l. (Box 8157)
- Universita Karlova. S. (Box 8158)
- Universitaet F. (Box 8159)
- Universitaet Hamburg (Box 8160)
- Universitaet Kiel. Institut fuer Weltwirtschaft (Probleme...) no. 50 (Box 8161)
- Universitaet Muenster. S. (Box 8162)
- Universitaet Zuerich (Box 8163)
- Universitair (Box 8164)
- Universitas Sumatera... (Box 8165)
- Universite catholique de Louvain (1835-1969). Faculte (Box 8166)
- Universite d'Amiens (Box 8167)
- Universite de Grenoble (Box 8168)
- Universite de Lyon (Box 8169)
- Universite de P. (Box 8170)
- Universite de Paris (subject) (Box 8171)
- Universite de Strasbourg (Box 8172)
- Universite l'Aurore (Box 8173)
- Universite P. (Box 8174)
- Universiti M. (Box 8175)
- University College, London (Box 8176)
- University of Adelaide (Box 8177)
- University of Birmingham (Box 8178)
- University of California, Berkeley. Publications in agriculture sciences (Box 8179)
- University of California, Berkeley. Center for R. (Box 8180)
- University of California, Berkeley. Modern (Box 8181)
- University of California, Los Angeles. Department of G. (Box 8182)
- University of California publications in g. (Box 8183)
- University of Cambridge. K. (Box 8184)
- University of Cambridge (Subject) -- Registers (Box 8185)
- University of Chicago (author) studies (Box 8186)
- University of Chicago. Oriental institute (Box 8187)
- University of Colorado. L. (Box 8188)
- University of Edinburgh (Box 8189)
- University of G. (Box 8190)